http://www.meadowmania.co.uk/privacy-policy

Home
Wild FlowersView All Wild FlowersWildflower Meadow SeedWildflower Seed 100% UK MixesBeautiful Wildflower MeadowsWildflower Mixes for BordersPerennial wild flower plug plantsWild flower plug plant mixturesWild Flower Bulbs (aut. planting)Cornfield annual seedUrban Pollinator Seed MixesWildflower Seed PacketsWildflower Seeds BulkBasic meadow mixMeadow Grass SeedLawn SeedView All Lawn SeedLarge amenity areasTop Quality lawnsGrass seed for Sports fields Woodland shady areas grass seed Miscellaneous amenity mixesLawn EquipmentGrass SeedHorsesClovers & Green ManuresNative HedgingBird Feed & Nest BoxesView All Bird Feed & Nest BoxesWild Bird Seed MixesBird & Insect Homes About us
News
Customer's Meadows
Login
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
What is this Privacy Policy for?
This privacy policy governs the privacy of this website www.meadowmania.co.uk and it's users who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
The Website
This website and it's owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website comply's to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.
Use of Cookies
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website.
Cookies are small files saved to the users computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the users interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through it's server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and it's external serving vendors.
This website uses tracking software to monitor it's visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information - http://www.google.com/privacy.html.
Contact & Communication
Users contacting this website and/or it's owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.
This website and it's owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
Email Newsletter
This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.
Subscriptions are taken in compliance with UK Spam Laws detailed in the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003. All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website. Under the Data Protection Act 1998 you may request a copy of personal information held about you by this website's email newsletter program.
Email marketing campaigns published by this website or it's owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation. This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based around their activity.
In compliance with UK Spam Laws and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 subscribers are given the opportunity to un-subscribe at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign.
External Links
Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links users should always adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.
The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and it's owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
Resources & Further Information
Data Protection Act 1998
Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 - The Guide
Written by James King at  Jamie King Media  © 2012 - v.2.0 February 2012 | Edited & customised by: MAS Seeds Ltd
